ILGWU Oral History 5780 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 279)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 279, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 280)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 280, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 281)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 281, Folder 1)
- David Zelinka (Box 282)
  - David Zelinka, 1975 (Box 282, Folder 1)
- David Zelinka (Box 283)
  - David Zelinka, 1975 (Box 283, Folder 1)
- David Gingold (Box 284)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 284, Folder 1)
- David Gingold (Box 285)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 285, Folder 1)
- David Gingold (Box 286)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 286, Folder 1)
- David Gingold (Box 287)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 287, Folder 1)
- David Gingold (Box 288)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 288, Folder 1)
- David Gingold (Box 289)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 289, Folder 1)
- David Gingold (Box 290)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 290, Folder 1)
- David Gingold (Box 291)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 291, Folder 1)
- David Gingold (Box 292)
  - David Gingold, 1974 (Box 292, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 293)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 293, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 294)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 294, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 295)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 295, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 296)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 296, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 297)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 297, Folder 1)
- William Ross (Box 298)
  - William Ross, 1975 (Box 298, Folder 1)
- Samuel Sandhaus (Box 299)
  - Samuel Sandhaus, 1975 (Box 299, Folder 1)
- Samuel Sandhaus (Box 300)
  - Samuel Sandhaus, 1975 (Box 300, Folder 1)
- Samuel Sandhaus (Box 301)
  - Samuel Sandhaus, 1975 (Box 301, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 302)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 302, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 303)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 303, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 304)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 304, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 305)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 305, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 306)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 306, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 307)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 307, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 308)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 308, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 309)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 309, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 310)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 310, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 311)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 311, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 312)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 312, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 313)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 313, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 314)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 314, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 315)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1975-1976 (Box 315, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 316)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 316, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 317)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 317, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 318)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 318, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 319)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 319, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 320)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 320, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 321)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 321, Folder 1)
- Bernard Shane (Box 322)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 322, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 323)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 323, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 324)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 324, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 325)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 325, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 326)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 326, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 327)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 327, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 328)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 328, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 329)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 329, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli (Box 330)
  - Antony Conticelli, 1975 (Box 330, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 331)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 331, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 332)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 332, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 333)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 333, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 334)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 334, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 335)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 335, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 336)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 336, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 337)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 337, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 338)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 338, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 339)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 339, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 340)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 340, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 341)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 341, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 342)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 342, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 343)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 343, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 344)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 344, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 345)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 345, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 346)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 346, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 347)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 347, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 348)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 348, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 349)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 349, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 350)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 350, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 351)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 351, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 352)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 352, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 353)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 353, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 354)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 354, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 355)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 355, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 356)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 356)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 356, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 357)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 357, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 358)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 358, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 359)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 359, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 360)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 360, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 361)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 361, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 362)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 362, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 363)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 363, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 364)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 364, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 365)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 365, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 366)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 366, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 367)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 367, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 368)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 368, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 369)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 369, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 370)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 370, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 371)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 371, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 372)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 372, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 373)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 373, Folder 1)
- Josephine Stern (Box 374)
  - Josephine Stern, 1976 (Box 374, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 375)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 375, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 376)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 376, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 377)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 377, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 378)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 378, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 379)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 379, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 380)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 380, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 381)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 381, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 382)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 382, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 383)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 383, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 384)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 384, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 385)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 385, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 386)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 386, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross (Box 387)
  - Murray Gross, 1976 (Box 387, Folder 1)
- Enrico Parenti (Box 388)
  - Enrico Parenti, 1974 (Box 388, Folder 1)
- Enrico Parenti (Box 389)
  - Enrico Parenti, 1974 (Box 389, Folder 1)
- Enrico Parenti (Box 390)
  - Enrico Parenti, 1974 (Box 390, Folder 1)
- Betha Mandel Lanxer (Box 391)
  - Bertha Mandel Laxner, 1978 (Box 391, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 392)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 392, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 393)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 393, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 394)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 394, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 395)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 395, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 396)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 396, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 397)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 397, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 398)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 398, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 399)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 399, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 400)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 400, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 401)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 401, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 402)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 402, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 403)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 403, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 404)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 404, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 405)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 405, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 406)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 406, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 407)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 407, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 408)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 408, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 409)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 409, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 410)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 410, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 411)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 411, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 412)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 412, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 413)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 413, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 414)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 414, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 415)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 415, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 416)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 416, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 417)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 417, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 418)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 418, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 419)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 419, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 420)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 420, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 421)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 421, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 422)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 422, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 423)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 423, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 424)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 424, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 425)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 425, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 426)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 426, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 427)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 427, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 428)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 428, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 429)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 429, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 430)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 430, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 431)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 431, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 432)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 432, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 433)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 433, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 434)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 434, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 435)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 435, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 436)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 436, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 437)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 437, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 438)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 438, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 439)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 439, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 440)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 440, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 441)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 441, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 442)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 442, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 443)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 443, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 444)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 444, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 445)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 445, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 446)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 446, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 447)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 447, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 448)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 448, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 449)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 449, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 450)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 450, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin (Box 451)
  - Abraham Plotkin, 1978 (Box 451, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 452)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 452, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 453)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 453, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 454)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 454, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 455)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 455, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 456)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 456, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 457)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 457, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 458)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 458, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 459)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 459, Folder 1)
- Frank Gatti (Box 460)
  - Frank Gatti, 1979 (Box 460, Folder 1)
- Shelley Appleton (Box 461)
  - Shelley Appleton, 1979 (Box 461, Folder 1)
- Samuel Weiss (Box 462)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981 (Box 462, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 463)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 463, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 464)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 464, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 465)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 465, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 466)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 466, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 467)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 467, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 468)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 468, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 469)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 469, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 470)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 470, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 471)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 471, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 472)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 472, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 473)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 473, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 474)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 474, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 475)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 475, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 476)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 476, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 477)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 477, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 478)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 478, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 479)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 479, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 480)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 480, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 481)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 481, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 482)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 482, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 483)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 483, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 484)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 484, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 485)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 485, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 486)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 486, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 487)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 487, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 488)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 488, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 489)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 489, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 490)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 490, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 491)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 491, Folder 1)
- Lazere Teper (Box 492)
  - Lazare Teper, 1981-1984 (Box 492, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 493)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 493, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 494)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 494, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 495)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 495, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 496)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 496, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 497)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 497, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 498)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 498, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 499)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 499, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 500)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 500, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 501)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 501, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 502)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 502, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 503)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 503, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 504)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 504, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 505)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 505, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 506)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 506, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 507)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 507, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 508)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 508, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 509)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 509, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 510)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 510, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 511)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 511, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 512)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 512, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 513)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 513, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 514)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 514, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 515)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 515, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 516)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 516, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 517)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 517, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 518)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 518, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 519)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 519, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 520)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 520, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 521)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 521, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 522)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 522, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 523)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 523, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 524)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 524, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 525)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 525, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 526)
  - Israel Breslow, 1981-1982 (Box 526, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 527)
  - Israel Breslow, 1982 (Box 527, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 528)
  - Israel Breslow, 1982 (Box 528, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 529)
  - Israel Breslow, 1982 (Box 529, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 530)
  - Israel Breslow, 1982 (Box 530, Folder 1)
- Sarah Borenstein (Box 531)
  - Sarah Borenstein, 1982 (Box 531, Folder 1)
    O.H. 25
- Sarah Borenstein (Box 532)
  - Sarah Borenstein, 1982 (Box 532, Folder 1)
- Mary Goff Shuster (Box 533)
  - Mary Goff Shuster, 1982 (Box 533, Folder 1)
    O.H. 26
- Mary Goff Shuster (Box 534)
  - Mary Goff Shuster, 1982 (Box 534, Folder 1)
- Jennie Silverman (Box 535)
  - Jennie Silverman, 1982 (Box 535, Folder 1)
    O.H. 27
- Clara Larsen (Box 536)
  - Clara Larsen, 1982 (Box 536, Folder 1)
    O.H. 28
- Clara Larsen (Box 537)
  - Clara Larsen, 1982 (Box 537, Folder 1)
- Joseph Roth (Box 538)
  - Joseph Roth, 1982 (Box 538, Folder 1)
    O.H. 29
- John Denaro (Box 539)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 539, Folder 1)
    O.H. 30
- John Denaro (Box 540)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 540, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 541)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 541, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 542)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 542, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 543)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 543, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 544)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 544, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 545)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 545, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 546)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 546, Folder 1)
- Michael Bachrach (Box 547)
  - Michael Bachrach, 1983 (Box 547, Folder 1)
    O.H. 31
- Jack Faier (Box 548)
  - Jack Faier, 1983 (Box 548, Folder 1)
    O.H. 32
- Benjamin Follman (Box 549)
  - Benjamin Follman, 1983 (Box 549, Folder 1)
    O.H. 33
- Benjamin Follman (Box 550)
  - Benjamin Follman, 1983 (Box 550, Folder 1)
- Harry Schindler (Box 551)
  - Harry Schindler, 1983 (Box 551, Folder 1)
    O.H. 34
- Harry Schindler (Box 552)
  - Harry Schindler, 1983 (Box 552, Folder 1)
- Harry Schindler (Box 553)
  - Harry Schindler, 1983 (Box 553, Folder 1)
- Graeber (Box 554)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, 1983 (Box 554, Folder 1)
    O.H. 35
- Graeber (Box 555)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, 1983 (Box 555, Folder 1)
- Graeber (Box 556)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, 1983 (Box 556, Folder 1)
- Graeber (Box 557)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, 1983 (Box 557, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 558)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 558, Folder 1)
    O.H. 36
- Morris Novik (Box 559)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 559, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 560)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 560, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 561)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 561, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 562)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 562, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 563)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 563, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 564)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 564, Folder 1)
- Graber & Goldstein (Box 565)
  - Ruth Rubinstein Graeber, Duegen Goldstein, Eugene Goldstein, and Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 565, Folder 1)
    O.H. 37
- Graeber & Goldstein (Box 566)
  - Ruth Rubinstein Graeber, Duegen Goldstein, Eugene Goldstein, and Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 566, Folder 1)
- Graeber & Goldstein (Box 567)
  - Ruth Rubinstein Graeber, Duegen Goldstein, Eugene Goldstein, and Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 567, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 568)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 568, Folder 1)
    O.H. 38
- Shrog (Box 569)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 569, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 570)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 570, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 571)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 571, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 572)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 572, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 573)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 573, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 574)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 574, Folder 1)
- Rosenberg (Box 575)
  - Rose Newmark Rosenberg, 1985 (Box 575, Folder 1)
    O.H. 39
- Fedorin (Box 576)
  - Rose Kaufman Fedorin, 1985 (Box 576, Folder 1)
    O.H. 40
- Fedorin (Box 577)
  - Rose Kaufman Fedorin, 1985 (Box 577, Folder 1)
- Fedorin (Box 578)
  - Rose Kaufman Fedorin, 1985 (Box 578, Folder 1)
- Schmidt (Box 579)
  - Fred Schmidt, 1985 (Box 579, Folder 1)
    O.H. 41
- Nathaniel Minkoff (Box 580)
  - Nathaniel Minkoff, 1975 (Box 580, Folder 1)
    O.H. 42
- Ida Weiss (Box 581)
  - Ida Weiss, 1986 (Box 581, Folder 1)
    O.H. 43
- Ida Weiss (Box 582)
  - Ida Weiss, 1986 (Box 582, Folder 1)
- Pauline Pepe (Box 583)
  - Pauline Pepe, 1986 (Box 583, Folder 1)
    O.H. 44
- Pauline Pepe (Box 584)
  - Pauline Pepe, 1986 (Box 584, Folder 1)
- Lula Read (Box 585)
  - Lula Read (Box 585, Folder 1)
    O.H. 45
- Lula Read (Box 586)
  - Lula Read (Box 586, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Schlesinger (Box 587)
  - Benjamin Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 587, Folder 1)
    O.H. 5; Use copy
- Benjamin Schlesinger (Box 588)
  - Benjamin Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 588, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Schlesinger (Box 589)
  - Benjamin Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 589, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Schlesinger (Box 590)
  - Benjamin Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 590, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Schlesinger (Box 591)
  - Benjamin Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 591, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Schlesinger (Box 592)
  - Benjamin Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 592, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Schlesinger (Box 593)